Are you sure Yuuta came down here?
本当にこっちに悠太が来たのか
I definitely saw him.
見たの　確かに
He wandered around this way.
ぶらぶらーってこっちの方に行くの
What a pain.
めんどくせーなー
見つからなかったら悠太を置いて帰るぞ
If we can't find him, let's leave without him.
I'm pretty sure he turned this—
確かこっちの角を曲がっ…
Oh, there he is!
あっ　いた
Yuuta...
ゆうたん
I like you!
好きです
よかったら私と付き合ってください
Please go out with me!
There's no way—
そんなの　誰が
Hey, everyone!
皆　こんなところにいたんですか
So that's where you were!
はい？
What?
Huh? Is that...
えっ　あれって　もしかして
Who is she? Is she a first year?
どこの女子だ　一年？
She's in our year.
I think her name's Takahashi-san.
同じ学年の子ですよ
確か高橋さんだったと思います
ダメですよ
W-We shouldn't be watching them like this!
こんな恋のデバガメは
Then we should talk to her outright.
じゃ　きちんと話を
No.
ダメ
It'll be fine as long as they don't find out.
大丈夫だって
本人にばれなきゃ
そういう問題じゃなくって
That's not the issue.
Oh.
What?
どうした
Yuuta's coming over here.
悠太がこっち来る
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
mattezu ni toozaketeita no wa atashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta kedo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作,仅供学习交流之用
若您喜欢本作品,请支持正版影像制品
---诸神字幕组---
日听 バサラ     翻译 景寒筱    日校 慧慧
总校 有明の月     时间轴 葛蔓     压制 PHENOTYPE
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
So... hot...
あちー
涼しい
Nice and cool.
ちょっと　なんなのこれ
What's with the heat?
September's already over, man!
もう９月も終わるっちゅうに
I can't believe that we're switching to our winter uniforms soon.
もうすぐ衣替えとか有り得ないよね
I know.
本当だよ　居眠りするたびに汗びっしょりかく
Imagine how I feel,
bathing in sweat every time I take a nap.
こっちの身にもなってほしいよ
That's not possible.
なれるか
よし　交替だ交替
Okay, let's trade.
I see it! I see it now!
All right. This time, I'll get it!
見える見える　よし　今度こそ
Come on. Rock, paper, scissors...
行くぞ　ジャンケン
Shoot!
ポン
ジャン
I lost again!
また
Three losses in a row!
三連敗
はいはい　早く早く
Yeah, yeah. Hurry up.
So hot...
熱い　熱い…
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot...
Can't you even shut up for a little bit?
うっせえな　少し黙れよ！
But it's so hot!
だっても熱いだもん
Looks like the heat's getting to them.
Super-ultra-executive-angelic-super hot!
二人とも熱さでいらついてますね
Kaname's like that throughout the entire year.
要はオールシーズンああだよ
It only feels hotter 'cause you won't shut up about it!
それより
Anyway...
Maybe having all these guys around without a girl in sight is making it feel even hotter.
そもそもさ　男だらけで女っ気がないのが熱さに拍車をかけているのかもね
Y-You're right. That must be it.
そ　そうだよね　それだよ
We're all second years.
もう皆高二なんだから　彼女の一人や二人
We should have one or two...
or maybe even three or four girlfriends by now, if that's your preference.
お好みで３人や４人
さっさと作りなさいよ
お好みでって
"If it's our preference," you say...
でもまあ　５人もいるんだから
But since there are five of us,
one of us might already have a girlfriend.
もしかしたらもう彼女がいたりするやつが
Maybe... one of us...
とか　なんて
Hey, I don't feel a breeze. Fan m--
ちょっと風が来ないよ
ちゃんと扇いでくだ…
What?
なに
Nothing.
いえ
もしかして話すつもりないの
He's not going to talk about it?
That must not have been a confession!
だから告白じゃなかったんですよ
They may have been rehearsing for a play or something.
演劇かなにかの練習で
That's ridiculous.
ありえねえだろう　祐希にはなにも話してねえのか
Yuuki, did he say anything to you?
No, and I tell Yuuta everything, too.
話してないよ
俺はなんでも悠太に話すのに
今はおめえと悠太の話してんじゃねえ
We're not talking about your relationship with Yuuta here.
あっ　そうそう　実は昨日さ
Oh, that reminds me.
Yesterday...
Yesterday?
昨日？
Co...
国
Co...?
告？
Could any of you have taken my dictionary out of my locker?
語辞典誰か俺のロッカーから持っていかなかった
すごい食いついたね今
You guys seemed awfully interested just now.
Yuuta.
悠太　この際だからはっきり聞くけど
I might as well ask since I have the opportunity.
昨日
Yesterday, co...
国
語辞典誰かに勝手に持っていたの???
Could someone have taken your dictionary?
バカ　お前はバカか
Stupid! You're just plain stupid!
同じジュースでも
I feel like juice tastes different from a cup than from a carton.
カンとコップだと味が違う気がする
氷のせいか
Maybe it's the ice, or maybe it's the straw.
ストローのせいか
それとも単なる気のせいか
Or maybe it's just my imagination.
But the biggest reason...
でも 一番の原因はこの音のせいだ
is because of this sound.
Next to an Apple
あーあ　ゆうたん本当に言わないつもりかな
Is Yuutan really not going to tell us?
Maybe he rejected her when she asked him out.
もしかして告白された時に断ったからかな
あー　あるなそれは
That could be it.
あははは　ありえないって
Who would ever turn down a girl who confessed to you?
女の子から告白されて断るなんて
Not even I've done that.
俺だってしたことないよ
Chizuru, I bet no one's ever confessed to you.
千鶴はそもそも告白されたことないでしょ
あっ　なんだとコラッ！
What did you say?!
Who do you think you're talking to?
誰に向かって言ってんだ
Calm down.
落ち着け
モテる男だぞこら
Yuutan, Shun-chan, let's go.
ゆうたん　春ちゃん　かーえろう
O-Okay.
あっ　はい
Yuutan, let's go.
ゆうたん　行くよ
あ えーっとですね
Actually, um...
I can't go home with you guys today.
実は今日は一緒に帰れないっていうか
用事が
I have something to do.
Something to do?
用事って
用事です
Something to do.
では皆さん帰りましょうか
Well, then. Shall we go?
S-Sure.
そ そうだな
Yuutan, see you later.
ゆうたん　じゃあねえ
じゃ　お先に
See you later.
What do we do? What do we do? What do we do?
どうする　どうする　どうする
What do we do?
どうする
You're asking me what we should do?
どうするって
多分どっかで待ち合わせているんでしょう
They must be meeting up somewhere.
普通は昇降口か
Normally, people meet up at the front entrance.
悠太に感づかれるから
Let's split up and meet up again down there, so Yuuta doesn't suspect anything.
一度ばらけて昇降口のところに集合
ラジャ　ラジャ　ラジャ
Roger.
R-Roger.
Takahashi-san.
高橋さん
ごめん　結構待った
Sorry. Were you waiting long?
Not at all.
ぜ　全然
An after-school date.
放課後デート
He should at least tell us if he's dating her.
付き合うなら報告ぐらいしろってんだよな
I'd never accept it, though.
しても認めないけどね
Ah, they're leaving! Come on, come on.
行っちゃう行っちゃう　行こ行こ
Wh-What? We're going to follow them?
ええ？　尾行するんですか
We really shouldn't be doing this.
ダメですよ　そんな
We can't just let this go,
now that he's keeping it secret from us.
秘密にされた以上野放しにしておけますか
よーし　いざ出じ…
Now, let's...
Keep it down!
でけぇんだよ　声が
Sorry. I'm just so young and eager.
すみません　ちょっとやる気と若さが弾けて
You, too.
お前も　なんだその堂々とした足取りは
You can't just walk out in the open like that.
いなくなった
They're gone.
あ、しまった　どっち行った
Crap! Which way did they go?
What are we gonna do? We lost them.
どうするんだよ　見失ったぞ
Um...
あのう　多分階段を下りていったと思います
I think they probably went down those stairs.
Shun, you're curious, too?
春も気になるんだね
Don't push me.
押すな　だからまじめに尾行しろ
We need to do this properly, or we'll be found out.
ばれるぞ
What do you mean, "Do this properly"?
まじめにって
It's not proper to do this in the first place...
尾行自体が間違った行為じゃ
結局ついてきたか
So they did follow us.
暇だな　あの人たちも
They must have nothing else to do.
E-Excuse me.
あのう
いいえ
Nothing.
Are you tired from the heat?
もしかして熱くてばてた
What? No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
うんん　全然　全然
どっか寄ってく
Do you want to go somewhere?
Oh, u-um...
えっと　えーっと
How about the bookstore?
じゃ　本屋さんに
The bookstore?
本屋
ん　じゃ　そうしよう
Let's do that, then.
Where's the closest one?
ここから一番近いのはどこかな
From here? Probably...
えーっと　ここら辺だと
When he asked if I wanted to go somewhere...
今の寄ってくって　もしかして
Hey, Squadsman Yuuki!
おーい　祐希隊員
Come back!  Don't go over there!
戻ってこーい　そっちは行っちゃダメだ
The bookstore.
本屋か
How unexpected.
意外ですね
ごめんね　いきなり本屋なんて
Sorry about suggesting the bookstore.
Next to an Apple
ほしいのあった
Is there something you wanna get here?
Yes.
Next to an Apple
I'll go buy this.
買ってくるね
待って
Wait.
Don't you hate getting the top one?
一番上のって嫌じゃない
俺絶対買わないけど
I would never buy it.
弟なんかすごいよ
My brother has some strange habits.
If there's only one copy left,
he'll go to another store.
１冊しか置いてなかったら他の店行くことあるもん
Heh, I'm sure you don't care about that, though.
って　だからなんだって話ですが
What should we do?
どうします
Everything seems to be progressing smoothly.
ここまで順調に進んでいるようですなあ
あわてることないですよ
There's no rush. We're still fragile teenagers.
俺たちまだまだガラスの１０代
Cracks can form so easily.
ひびが入るのはたやすいさ
But Yuutan's not making any mistakes.
でも悠太全然へましないじゃん
まあ　悠太だからな
Well, it is Yuuta, after all...
So, which one of you did that?
おい　どっちだ
春のおてんば
Shun, how rude.
You shouldn't do that, Shun-chan.
ダメだよ　春ちゃん
What? I-I didn't do anything!
僕じゃないです
Who did it?!
どっちだって聞いてんだ
あの人たちどこまでついて来るんだろう
How long are they going to follow me?
You like books?
本好きなんだ
うん 休みの日はなんかいつも本読んでばかりで
Yes.
I end up reading all day when we don't have school.
悠太君は休みの日何してるの
Yuuta-kun, what do you do on your days off?
俺？　なにしてるかな
Me?
I dunno...
CD聞くか　弟の買い物付き合うか
Listen to CDs, go shopping with my brother,
弟がゲームしてるのを後ろから見てるか
watch my brother play video games...
なんもやってないな
I don't really do anything.
私も本ばっかりだよ
All I do is read.
本屋さん行ったり
I go to the bookstore... and the library.
図書館行ったり
地味ですみません
I'm sorry I'm not more interesting.
なんで
Why? What's wrong with that?
いいじゃん　ちゃんと好きなことがあって
You have something that you love doing.
Unlike Yuuki, I don't really have anything like that.
俺祐希と違って　そういうのないし
CD聞くって言っても　ジャケ買いした一枚しかないし
（ジャケ買い＝不是下载买的，而是自己专门去店买过来的
所以这里的“CD聞く”意味着“听音乐”的意思）
I said that I listen to CDs, but I only have the one I bought because I liked the cover.
It's not even that great, so I don't listen to it much.
それも割と好きってくらいだから　あんまり聞かないし
Oh, but...
でも私も本は好きだけど
I like books, but I don't like every book I own.
持ってる本全部好きなわけじゃないよ
読み返さないやつもいっぱいあるし
I have a bunch that I've only read once.
And I don't think it's bad to only own one CD.
それにCD一枚しかないからって　悪いことなんてないと思う
Oh, I'm sorry. I just babbled on...
ごめん　なんか私一人で
Sorry!
ごめん
I'll... lend you that CD sometime.
今度そのCD貸し　ます
Okay.
Come on, Shun-chan. You should also write a text that we can send to Yuutan!
ほら　春ちゃんもゆうたんに送るメール準備して
What? Let's not do this.
ええ　やめましょうよ
Yuuta always has his phone on silent,
悠太いつもマナーモードにしてるから
so he'll just ignore any messages we send him.
いくら送っても無視されるだけだよ
Then the text bombing plan won't work!
メール波状攻撃作戦はダメかー
The enemy's a tough one, Squadsman Shun-chan!
敵は手強いぞ　春ちゃん隊員
The enemy?
敵って
もうちょっと普通に祝福してあげましょうよ
Why can't we just be happy for him, like normal people?
It's pretty cold of him to not tell us,
なにも言ってもらえなかったのも
そりゃ寂しいかもしれないですけど
but we should be happy that our friend has found love.
友達が両想いになれたんですから
Love?
両想い？
ゆうたんあの子のこと好きだったの
You're saying that Yuutan likes her?
That's the first I've heard of it.
What? But if he doesn't, why would he go out with her?
でもじゃなきゃ告白OKなんかしないんじゃ
Come on! Even if he doesn't like her,
there are other reasons to go out with her!
いやいや　あるでしょう
好きじゃなくてもOKなパターンも
What are you doing with your hands?
その手は一体
Well, yeah, that does happen,
but I don't know about Yuuta.
まぁ 確かにそういうのもあるらしいけど
悠太はどうだろうな
やはりそれを知るためには盗聴しかないか
The only way to know is to eavesdrop.
We can throw a paper cup phone in...
糸電話を投げ込んで
That would bother the other customers.
それは他の客様のご迷惑になりますので
Oh, he was just kidding—
いや　冗談で
Hush, you really are bothering people.
シ　本当ご迷惑だから
How long have you been there?
いつからそこに
君たちこそいつまでここに
How long are you going to follow me?
H-Have you known the whole time?
もしかしてずっと
It was obvious.
ばればれです
Where's your girlfriend?
彼女さんは
高橋さん　帰ったよ
Takahashi-san? She went home.
You should at least walk her home!
そこはお前送ってけよ
Aren't you dating?
付き合ってるんだろう
Ah, could it be that you don't actually like her, Yuutan?
もしかしてゆうたん
あの子のこと好きじゃないんじゃ
なのにOKしたから
But you accepted her confession anyway,
which is why you couldn't tell us?
俺らに言いづらかったんじゃないの
Hey, Chizuru-kun, don't say that.
えーちょっと　千鶴君　そんこと言っちゃダメですよ
Well, Yuutan?
ねね　悠太　どうなの
あの　ポテトが
Um...
Your fries.
Such a waste!
あっ　もったいない　バクッ
Munch, munch!
Ah, Chizuru-kun, don't eat things off of the floor!
千鶴君　ダメですよ　拾ったの食べたりしちゃ
You And I
Um...
ええと
Hold the other side.
そっち持って
I felt relieved when I heard his voice.
その声にほっとしました
そして　ドキドキしました
But also a bit nervous.
Are you okay?
大丈夫
大
I'm...
You're...?
大？
丈夫です
I'm fine.
でも　告白しようとかそんなのは全然なくて
But I never planned on confessing to him.
How'd it go with Yuuta-kun?
どうなったの　悠太君と
Huh?
You finally asked him out?
I was wondering when you would.
あ　やっと聞いてくれた
私もいつ聞こうかと思ってて
Me, too.
私も
We went out for tea the other day.
この前一緒にお茶したりしたよ
What? But Takahashi,
you're terrible at making conversation.
ええ　でも高橋しゃべるの全然ダメじゃん
Did you just drink in silence?
大沈黙だったんじゃないの
Did you just look at your phones the whole time?
もしかして二人で携帯激見的な
You have to try to talk to him.
がんばって話さないとダメだよ
高橋特に引っ込み思案だから
Takahashi, you're too shy.
でも悠太君結構話振ってくれたから
Well, Yuuta-kun's pretty talkative.
He's nice. I had fun.
やさしいし
楽しかったよ
I see.
そっか
Th-That's great.
よ　よかったじゃん
そういやさ　私和太鼓始めたんだよね最近
By the way, I started playing Taiko drums recently.
Taiko?
和太鼓
マジ？
Yeah, it's actually pretty fun.
あのね　結構はまるんだよ
Takahashi, is something wrong?
高橋　どうかした
No.
Ah, we have contemporary literature next.
次現国じゃん
Oh no, I need to borrow a textbook!
やばい　教科書借りてこなきゃ
Me, too.
私も私も
What? You forgot yours, Jun-chan?
ええ　純ちゃんも忘れたの
I'm going to the bathroom.
先にお手洗い行っとこ
Me, too.
私も行く
Really? You wanna come with?
そう　ついてくる
Sure.
うん　行く
Here's the CD I said I'd lend you.
はい　CD
貸すって言ってたやつ
Thank—
ありが
It's Wednesday. Contemporary literature's on Thursday!
今日水曜
現国は木曜じゃん
Jun-chan, you were freaking out, too.
純ちゃんだってあわててたくせに
Th-Thanks.
ありがとう
６曲目とかいいよ
The sixth track's pretty good.
バラードっぽいけど　俺は結構好き
It's a bit like a ballad, but I like it.
Jun-chan, over here!
純ちゃん　こっち
え　なに
What?
Hurry up!
早く
What is it?
Just hurry!
いいから
A-Are there any songs on it you would recommend?
CDお薦めの曲とかある
What? Yeah, the sixth track...
６曲目が　まあ
I see. I look forward to listening to it.
そうなんだ　楽しみ
あ　ひびが
There's a crack in it.
ごめんなさい　弁償します
I'm so sorry! I'll buy you a new one. I'm sorry!
ごめんなさい
It's fine. It's not like the CD inside broke.
いいよ　中身が割れたわけじゃないし
でも　でも
But... But...
It's...
大　丈夫　です
It's... okay.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
お待たせ　遅くなってごめんなさい
全然
Don't sweat it.
友達は
What about your friends?
What?
うん　今日はもう皆帰ったから
Oh, they've already gone home.
Everything's going smoothly, Squadsman Shun-chan.
順調のようですね　春ちゃん隊員
Let's stop this already.
もうやめましょうよ
とか言いながら　お前も見てんじゃねえか
You're still spying on them, even as you say that.
帰ろう
Let's go.
What?
Let's just go.
今日は帰ろう
CDさ
The CD...
What? I'm sorry! I'll replace it.
はい　ごめんなさい　弁償
That's not what I meant.
じゃなくて
When you return it, you can just put it in my locker.
返す時俺のロッカーん中入れといてくれればいいから
What?
Jeez, I never thought Takahashi would pull this off.
あーあ　でもまさか高橋がうまくいくなんてね
What? You're regretting it now?
なに　今になって
惜しいことしたとか思ってんの
You're the one who told her to confess.
告白しろって言ったの純ちゃんじゃん
I was just baiting her. I didn't think she'd actually do it.
ノリよノリ
だってまさかって思うじゃない
We're talking about Yuuta-kun.
相手は悠太君だよ
Wow, you thought he'd reject her. You're awful!
うわ　振られると思ってたんだ　性格わるー
I was convinced he'd turn her down, too.
でもあたしも思ってたんたな
どう考えても振られるって
I know, right?
でしょう
Takahashi-san.
高橋さん
Let's wait a bit before we go.
もうちょっとしてから帰ろうか
その時気づきました
That was when I realized...
Yuuta-kun always knew.
悠太君はずっと前から分かっていたって
なんで　帰ろう
Why? Let's go.
Takahashi, hurry.
高橋　早く
O-Okay.
I could barely keep up with them.
皆について行くのがやっとで
告白しちゃいなってば
Just tell him how you feel.
I'm sure he'll say yes. You're really cute!
絶対うまくいくって
高橋かわいいもん
I didn't want them to hate me.
嫌われたくなくて
こんな　こんな
I...
I look so stupid...
格好悪い私　全部
All of it...
Sorry, Yuuta-kun.
ごめんね　悠太君
Thank you for not rejecting me, and the rest of it...
振らないでいてくれたり
いろいろなんか
Don't worry about it.
いえ
それは　お気になさらず
I knew my friends were saying those things behind my back.
気付いてはいたの
私がいないところで友達がああいうこと言ってるって
だけどね　情けないと思うかもしれないけど
But even though you might think this is pathetic, I just can't break away from them.
皆から離れるのもやっぱりできなくてね
Sure.
I'm scared of being alone.
やっぱり怖いし　一人になるのとか
Besides, there are times when I have fun being with them.
それに一緒にいて楽しいって思う瞬間だってちゃんとあるの
Yeah.
You don't need to force yourself away from them.
無理に頑張って離れなくても
皆のこと嫌いじゃないから
If you don't dislike them, you should stay with them.
一緒にいてもいいと思うよ
The CD—
CDさ
Sorry, I'll replace it!
はい　ごめんなさい　弁償
That's not what I was going to say.
じゃなくて
I think it grew on me.
あのCD　俺　前より好きになってると思う
なんか　好きになれたわ
I came to like it.
I wouldn't say I love it yet, though.
まだ大好きまではいってないけど
I think if you change a little,
高橋さんが少し変われば
you might have more fun with your friends.
友達と一緒にいるのがもっと楽しくなるかもしれないし
You might even grow to like them.
好きになるかもしれないし
I think it'd be nice if that happened.
そうなるといいよねって
俺は思う
Yuuta-kun.
悠太君
I just keep saying "I think, I think..."
思うだけかよって感じですが
Sorry.
すみません
Oh, um, no need! I have my own.
鼻
いいえ　その　自分のあるんで
Huh? Y-You broke up?
ええ？　わ　別れました
Yeah.
That was quick. Why?
早
なんで
Because he couldn't handle the silence, obviously.
沈黙に耐えかねたに決まってるじゃん
そんな簡単じゃないよ　恋は
Love's not that simple.
なによ　それ
Where'd that come from?
Takahashi, you're so cheeky!
高橋生意気
Summer is... ending.
夏が終わる
しかし　この秋の涼しさは
But is the coolness of autumn answering the hearts of those who have been rejected, perhaps?
振られん坊将軍には余計答えちゃうのかな
まあ　俺らに内緒にしなければ
Well, this wouldn't have happened
if you hadn't kept it secret from us.
こんなことにもならなかったはずだよ
そこ　肝に銘じておくように
Remember that!
Okay, okay.
じゃ　お詫びにジュース奢ってあげるよ
I'll buy you some juice to make up for it.
Really?
まじで
I can only afford one, though, so you'll have to share.
でもお金なくて　１本しか買えないから
皆で回して飲んでね
W-What?
Bam.
Hey...
Hey, I almost experienced my first backache just now.
お兄ちゃんこの年でぎっくり腰デビューするとこだったよ
I'll go with you.
付き合ってあげる
いいよ　重いし
No, you're too heavy.
Who cares? It's a date.
いいじゃん　デート　デート
I feel like juice tastes different from a cup than from a carton.
同じジュースでも
かんとコップだと
味が違う気がする
Maybe it's the ice, or maybe it's the straw.
氷のせいか
ストローのせいか
単なる気のせいか
Or maybe it's just my imagination.
Asaba Yuuta
But the biggest reason is because of this sound.
でも一番の原因は
この音のせいだ
僕は泣き虫で　悔しくて
好不甘心只当个爱哭鬼
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
だけどあなたに今伝えたいんだ
想把这种心情传达给你
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
ただまっすぐに僕を見つめる
请不要移开目光注视着我吧
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
強くて優しいその瞳に応えるために
让我可以回应你坚强而温柔的眼神
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
Giving me the chance to answer you and the strength and tenderness in your eyes
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
you taught me about what I lost sight of
いつしか見失ってた
不知不觉就丢失了
一番大切なものも
最珍惜的事物
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
そっとあなたが教えてくれた
然而你教我如何找回它
たしかにそう思えるから
我发自肺腑地这么觉得
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
僕は弱虫で　嫌だった
好讨厌我的懦弱
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta n dakedo
I hated how weak I was
だけどもっともっと強くなるから
所以想要变得更强
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
あなたのことを守れるような僕になるから
成为能够守护你的人
anata no koto mo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you and me both
所以 请稍稍等我一下吧
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me
Next time: "Daily Wage Hero."
Daily Wage Hero
"Senpai and I."
Senpai and I